http://www.hisglassworks.com/privacy-notice/

10” glass blade
(1209)
7 5” diamond blade
(1425)
7” diamond saw blade for glass
(1699)
7 5” diamond bladehow
(1400)
Recent Searches
23mm sintered
(548)
Diamond spo
(1262)
Diamond str
(1262)
10 glass blade
(1205)
Account
Sign In
Skip to Content
Your work leaves.
Your tools live with you.
My Quote
His Glassworks, Inc
Menu
GrindingDisksDisks for Lap GrindersElectroplated Diamond Disks24 Inch20 Inch18 Inch16 Inch14 Inch12 Inch10 Inch8 InchStarLap Diamond Disks24 Inch18 Inch12 InchDiamond Smoothing Pads24 Inch20 Inch18 Inch16 Inch14 Inch12 Inch10 Inch8 Inch28 Inch 30 InchElectroStatic Diamond Disks12 Inch8 InchLP66 Polishing PadSynthetic Felt Pads3M Cerium DiskPolpur MJ Flat Laps for PumiceDisks for Right Angle GrindersTornado DisksBaby RokCeramica3M Plated2 Inch4 Inch5 InchDiamond Smoothing2 inch4 Inch5 Inch3M Electrostatic2 Inch4 Inch5 InchPolpur Lapi-T2 Inch4 InchSnail LockPolishingConvex Diamond Pads3 Inch4 InchDisks for Hand Held Grinders3M PlatedPSA BackedVelcro BackedDual Lock BackedDiamond SmoothingVelcro BackedDual Lock BackedDisk AccessoriesBacker Pads2 Inch3 Inch4 Inch5 InchMandrelsDisk OrganizerCeriumWheelsRadiused WheelsSpherical MiracleItalian Electroplated RadiusElectroplated RadiusedSintered RadiusedDiamond Smoothing on MH-TDiamond Smoothing on FeltPolpur Lapi-TFeltRadiusedDiamond Smoothing on Felt SubstrateFlat Edged WheelsSintered Diamond Flat Edge WheelsDiamondBackCrystal RingDiamond SmoothingPolpur Lapi-TFeltEngraving WheelsSintered WheelsVIDV-Wheel (miter)Straight Edge (strap)VID Full Circle (olive)DiasV-WheelFull CircleDressing SticksMerker Engraving SpindlesElectroplated WheelsV-WheelStraight EdgeFull CirclePolpur Lapi-TV-WheelStraight EdgeFull Circle (Olive Cut)Polpur Engraving KitFeltPumice WheelsExpanding DrumsBeltsFor Expanding Drums6 x 1-1/2 DrumsElectrostatic DiamondDiamond SmoothingFelt6 x 2-1/2 DrumsSilicon CarbidePlated DiamondElectrostatic DiamondDiamond SmoothingTrizactCerium ImpregnatedCorkFelt8 x 3 DrumsSilicon CarbidePlated DiamondElectrostatic DiamondDiamond SmoothingTrizactCorkFeltCerium ImpregnatedFor Tabletop Belt Sanders3 x 41-1/2 Inch BeltsSilicon
CarbidePlated DiamondResin Diamond Smoothing BeltsElectrostatic DiamondTrizact BeltsCorkCerium ImpregnatedFelt3 x 25-7/32 Inch BeltsSilicon CarbidePlated DiamondElectrostatic
DiamondDiamond
SmoothingTrizactFeltCerium ImpregnatedFor Upright Belt SandersSilicon CarbideSinglePack of 5Plated DiamondElectrostatic DiamondResin DiamondTrizactSinglePack of 5Cork BeltsFeltCerium ImpregnatedHand GrindingHand Pads3M PlatedSintered DiamondDiamond SmoothingCerium ImpregnatedHand BlockHandipads3M PlatedDiamond SmoothingCerium Impregnated3M Diamond FilesPlastic FilesVelcro FilesCones and DomesConesElectroplatedDiamond SmoothingPolpur MTVPolishingDomesElectroplatedDiamond SmoothingPolpur MTVPolishingBladesSlabbing BladesHusqvarna Superlok GMDressing StickMedium Cut BladesResult BladesMK-303 BladesDressing StickFine Cut BladesHusqvarna Superlok Glass+MK-215GLResin BladesSuper Thin Kerf Diamond BladesDressing StickTaurus BladesRevolution XT BladesStandard BladeGlass BladeDressing StickSlittersElectroplated SlittersSintered SlittersBlade AccessoriesWet Circular Saw BladesDrillsSmall Diameter DrillsTriple Ripple DrillsElectroplated Core DrillsDiamond Sure Electroplated Core DrillsCrystalite Electroplated Core DrillsSintered Core DrillsSintered Core DrillsSink Kits and HonesSink DrainDiamond HonesPoints and BitsElectroplated Carving Points1/16" Shank3/32" Shank1/8" Shank1/4" ShankPoint KitsShaped BitsSintered Carving Points3/32" Shank1/8" ShankSintered Ball BitsDisks, Bands, and Shaped tools3M Plated DisksPSA BackedVelcro BackedDual Lock BackedSmoothing DisksVelcro BackedDual Lock BackedEverRun BandsPlated Diamond3/8 Inch Bands1/2 Inch Bands1 Inch BandsSmoothing PointsShaped BitsPolpur Lapi-T PointsSlittersElectroplated SlittersSintered SlittersMachineryFlat GrindersSmall GrindersLarge GrindersCovington GrindersSteinert GrindersWaterJet Design grindersRociprolapsFlat Lap AccessoriesRociprolap AccessoriesFaceting ArmHand GrindersElectric GrindersPneumatic GrindersFlexible Shaft GrindersHand Grinder AccessoriesBacker Pads2 Inch3 Inch4 Inch5 InchFlexible Shaft AccessoriesForedomSuhnerRight Angle Grinder AccessoriesCompressorsLathesGrinding LathesPolishing LathesLathe PartsWet Belt SandersVertical Belt SandersTabletop Belt SandersFloor Standing Belt SandersHorizontal Belt SandersBelt Sander Accessories and PartsWet SawsSmall Wet SawsLarge Wet SawsRing SawsWet Circular SawsSaw Parts and AccessoriesRing Saw PartsTaurus II.2Taurus 3Revolution XTHusqvarna Saw PartsMK Saw PartsSandblastersTabletop Sandblast CabinetsCabinet BlastersKit SpecialsCabinet Blaster AdditionsSandblaster Parts and AccessoriesCompressorsSurfacingAdhesivesEpoxiesHXTAL NYL-1XTR-311Pre-Treatment and RemovalA-1100ATTACKMixing SuppliesCupsScalesStirs and dispensersHang Your GlassAcid EtchingVari-Etch PowderVari-Etch CreamButtercut ResistCoating ProductsTapes and MasksAbrasivesSilicon Carbide1 Pound5 Pound50 PoundPumice1 Pound5 Pound50 PoundGarnetWhitingPolishingCer-Optik Cerium OxideCeri-Tec Cerium OxideCerox 1663 Cerium OxideSuperox 100T Cerium Oxide3M Cerium Slurry (pre-mixed)Ax Cerium OxideGearLoc-LineFor Lapping DisksFor WheelsFor MachinesFor Your GlassT-ShirtsGift CertificatesLightingHealth and SafetyFor YourselfRespiratorsApronsFor Your StuffHang Your GlassLocking Stand-offsNesting Stand-offsRound Stand-offsSuper Duty Stand-OffsBooksGlassKItsSpecialsDisksMachinerySupportFrequently Asked QuestionsHXTAL Education PromotionProduct ManualsProduct Safety Data SheetsCovid-19 UpdateContact UsVideos–DisksHow Electroplated Diamond Disks WorkHow Smoothing Pads WorkHow Polishing Pads WorkThe Best First Grind Steps for Diamond DisksVideos–DrillsUsing Sintered Core Drills With a Drill Head AssemblyVideos–AdhesivesUsing HXTAL as a Clear Coat on GlassMixing and Using HXTAL to Laminate GlassVideos–MachineryMaintaining Your Lap Grinder Wheel HeadSetting Up a Covington 761 Wet Belt SanderSetting Up a Covington 12 Inch Lap GrinderSetting Up an MK-101 Wet Tile Saw Faceting A Marble With A LapDancer Faceting ArmVideos–Loose AbrasivesUsing Pumice on Your GlassVideos–Etching and CoatingUsing Vari-Etch Powder and Cream to Etch Your GlassCoating Sandblasted Surfaces with Liquid LusterVideos–SawbladesWater Usage with Glass Specific Diamond BladesHow to Use a Dressing Stick on Your Diamond BladeBlade Choices for Millefore CutsVideos–How to...Making a Drinking Glass from a Wine BottleGrinding a Cast Glass Surface With a Right Angle GrinderUsing a Rociprolap to Grind and Polish GlassGrinding Glass from Rough Grind to Final Polish
Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of His Glassworks site visitors and customers.
This privacy policy applies where His Glassworks is acting as data controller with respect to the personal data of our visitors and customers.
We currently do utilize cookies on our website to facilitate the ordering process. Our cookie connects to the following information:
Shopping cart products
Recently view products
Customer group
All information in the cookie is anonymized and does not contain any personal data.
1. How we use your personal data
We may process data about your use of our website including your IP address, geographical, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths. The source of the usage data is Google Analytics. The legal basis for this processing is for the monitoring and improvement of our website and services.
We may process your personal data including your name, address, telephone number, and email address for the purpose of completing your order in a timely and correct manner and for communication in case there is any issue with your account or order status.
We may process your personal data including your name and email address for your opt-in subscription to our email newsletter. Subscription to our email newsletter is purely optional and can be stopped at any time through the ‘unsubscribe’ mechanism on the newsletter. Removal from the email system can also be requested directly from His Glassworks.
We may process information related to any communication that you send to us including communication content and meta data associated with the communication. The corresponding data may be processed for the purpose of communicating with you and for record-keeping purposes for the proper administration of our business.
We may process any of your personal data where necessary for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out of court proceeding.
2. Providing your personal data to others
We may disclose your name, address, phone number, and email address to our suppliers insofar as reasonably necessary to facilitate the shipment and delivery of ordered products when necessary.
We will share transaction data with our payment service providers only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing your payments, refunding said payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds.
In addition to the specific disclosures of personal data set out in this Section, we may disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another person.
3. Retaining and deleting personal data
Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.
In most cases it is not possible for us to specify in advance the periods for which your personal data will be retained. We may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another person.
4. Amendments
We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website.
5. Your rights
Your principal rights under data protection law are:
The right to access
The right to rectification
The right to erasure
The right to restrict processing
The right to data portability
The right to withdraw consent
Some of these rights are complex and not all of the details have been included in our summaries. Accordingly, you should read the relevant laws and guidance from the regulatory authorities for a full explanation of these rights.
You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not we process your personal data and, where we do, access to the personal data, together with certain additional information. That additional information includes details of the purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned and the recipients of the personal data. Providing the rights and freedoms of others are not affected, we will supply to you a copy of your personal data. The first copy will be provided free of charge, but additional copies may be subject to a reasonable fee.
You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed.
In some circumstances you have the right to the erasure of your personal data without undue delay. Those circumstances include: [the personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed; you withdraw consent to consent-based processing; you object to the processing under certain rules of applicable data protection law; the processing is for direct marketing purposes; and the personal data have been unlawfully processed]. However, there are exclusions of the right to erasure. The general exclusions include where processing is necessary: [for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information; for compliance with a legal obligation; or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims].
In some circumstances you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. Those circumstances are: you contest the accuracy of the personal data; processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure; we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of our processing, but you require personal data for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; and you have objected to processing, pending the verification of that objection. Where processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store your personal data. However, we will only otherwise process it: with your consent; for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person; or for reasons of important public interest.
You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation, but only to the extent that the legal basis for the processing is that the processing is necessary for: the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of any official authority vested in us; or the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party. If you make such an objection, we will cease to process the personal information unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims
You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes (including profiling for direct marketing purposes). If you make such an objection, we will cease to process your personal data for this purpose.
If you consider that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your habitual residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.
To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal information is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal.
You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by written notice to us
6. Our Details
This website is owned and operated by His Glassworks, Inc.
Our facility is located at 2000 Riverside Dr, Suite 19, Asheville NC 28804
You can contact us by phone at 828-254-2559 and through our website at https://www.hisglassworks.com/support/contact-us/
His Glassworks, Inc.
© 2020 His Glassworks, Inc. All rights reserved.
